(Howard:)Yes, you're delicious caramel too.
(Penny:)I will tell you why it's wrong--
(Sheldon:)-Excuse me, may I interject?
-What?
(Sheldon:)Biologically speaking,
Howard is perfectly justified...
(Sheldon:)...in seeking out the optimum mate
for the propagation of his genetic line.
(Howard:)Thank you, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Whether that propagation
is in the interest of humanity...
...is an entirely different question.
IRA [OVER RADIO]: This is Ira Flatow and
you're listening to NPR's Science Friday.
(Radio:)Joining us today by phone
from his office in Pasadena, California...
[AIR HISSING]
(Radio:)...is Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
Oh, this is gonna be a riot.
[AIR HISSING]
(Radio:)Thanks for being with us today,
Dr. Cooper.
(Sheldon:)My pleasure, Ira.
(Ira:)Now, let's talk
about magnetic monopoles.
(Ira:)Can you explain to our audience
just what a monopole is?